老·友·记
S01E01  The One Where Monica Gets a New Roommate
第一季第一集  瑞秋驾到
■
字幕制作
Subtitled By
@张纳德nerd
■
讨论邮箱
Discuss
f6dicuss@163.com (或私信)
■
老友记主题咖啡店(北京)
Central Perk (BeiJing)
朝阳区朝阳门外大街乙6号朝外SOHO A座0616室
■
老友记主题咖啡店(上海)
Central Perk (ShangHai)
虹口区哈尔滨路160号1913 老洋行A105号
■
老友记主题咖啡店(广州)
Central Perk (GuangZhou)
即将开业...
■
官方微博
Sina Weibo
@Central_Perk, @老友记主题店上海店
■
鸣谢
Special Thanks
Psychd(英文字幕)
There's nothing to tell. It's just some guy I work with.
没什么好八卦的 一个同事而已
Come on. You're going out with a guy.
拜托 都和你约会了
There's gotta be something wrong with him.
他一定是有什么毛病
So does he have a hump and a hairpiece?
他是驼背吗 还是戴假发
Wait. Does he eat chalk?
慢着 他吃粉笔吗
Just I don't want her to go through what I went through with Carl.
我不想莫妮卡 重蹈我和卡尔的覆辙
Okay, everybody relax.
你们都阳光点好吗
This is not even a date.
这根本不算是约会
It's just two people going out to dinner and not having sex.
只是一起吃个饭 没上床
Sounds like a date to me.
听着像是我的约会
I'm back in high school,
梦到我在上高中
in the middle of the cafeteria...
在一个咖啡店里
...and I realize I'm totally
然后突然发现 我全身都是...
naked.
光着的
-Oh, yeah.  -I've had that dream.
-我也梦到过  -我也是
Then I look down and I realize there is a phone...
然后我低头一看 看到一个电话...
...there.
正好在那儿
-Instead of...  -That's right!
-你确定不是...  -我确定
That one, I've never had.
这我可没梦到过
All of a sudden, the phone starts to ring.
突然 电话响了起来
And it turns out it's my mother.
居然是我妈打来的
Which is very, very weird because...
这真是太奇怪了 因为...
...she never calls me.
她从来没给我打过
This guy says "hello," I wanna kill myself.
听他打招呼 我都想自残了
Are you okay, sweetie?
你还好吧 老哥
I feel like someone grabbed my small intestine, pulled it out of my mouth...
我感觉像 有人把我肠子从嘴里拽出来...
...and tied it around my neck.  -Cookie?
-然后用肠子勒死我  -要饼干不
Carol moved her stuff out today.
卡罗今天搬走了
-Let me get you some coffee.  -Thanks.
-给你拿杯咖啡吧  -谢了
No. No, don't! Stop cleansing my aura.
停 停 别净化我的灵气了
Just leave my aura alone, okay?
别管我的灵气了好吗
I'll be fine. All right? Really. I hope she'll be very happy.
我会没事的 只要她能幸福就好
-No, you don't.  -No, I don't.
-不是吧  -必须不是啊
To hell with her. She left me!
去死吧 居然把我给甩了
And you never knew she was a lesbian.
你一直不知道她是女同性恋吗
No! Okay?
不知道 有问题吗
Why does everyone keep fixating on that?
你们咋都揪住这个不放了
She didn't know. How should I know?
她自己都不知道 我上哪儿知道去啊
Sometimes I wish I was a lesbian.
有时候 我也挺想当个女同性恋的
Did I say that out loud?
有这么大声音吗
All right, Ross. Look...
别这样 罗斯
...you're feeling a lot of pain right now.
我知道你现在很受伤...
You're angry. You're hurting.
怒火中烧 心如刀绞
Can I tell you what the answer is?
知道你现在最需要什么吗
Strip joints!
脱衣俱乐部
Come on, you're single. Have some hormones.
拜托 你现在单身了 荷尔蒙一定爆棚了吧
See, but I don't want to be single, okay?
我不想单身好吗
I just wanna be married again.
我现在只想...再找个老婆
And I just want a million dollars!
我要100万美刀就行
Rachel?
瑞秋吗
Oh, God, Monica! Hi! Thank God!
莫妮卡 总算找到你了
I went to your building  and you weren't there.
我去公寓没找到你
and this guy with a hammer said...
然后一个拿锤子的人说...
...that you might be here, and you are.
...你可能在这里 幸好你真的在
-Can I get you some coffee?  -Decaf.
-请问您点咖啡吗  -无咖啡因的
Okay, everybody, this is Rachel
给你们介绍一下 这是瑞秋
another Lincoln High survivor.
我的高中同学
This is everybody. This is Chandler and Phoebe...
这些是我的朋友 钱德 菲比
...and Joey.
那边的是乔伊
And remember my brother, Ross?
记得罗斯吧 我哥哥
-Sure!  -Hey.
-当然  -你好
Oh, God.
抱歉
So you wanna tell us now
打算现在告诉我们吗
or are we waiting for four wet bridesmaids?
还是说再等一下伴娘
Oh, God! Well, it started about a half-hour before the wedding.
好吧 这得从婚礼开始前半个小时说起
I was in this room with all the presents...
我当时在礼品间里呆着
...and I was looking at this gravy boat.
然后我看到了一个船形肉卤盘
This really gorgeous Limoges gravy boat.
这个船形肉卤盘特别的好看
When all of a sudden... Sweet 'N Low?
可是突然之间...放糖了吗
I realized...
我意识到...
...I was more turned on by this gravy boat than by Barry.
相比于巴瑞 我对这个肉卤盘更有感觉
Then I got really freaked out, and that's when it hit me:
然后我吓坏了 而且突然想到
How much Barry looks like Mr. Potato Head.
巴瑞长得特别像土豆先生(玩具总动员)
You know, I mean, I always knew he looked familiar, but...
我一直觉得他眼熟 没想到...
Anyway, I just had to get out of there, and I started wondering:
总之 我当时必须离开 同时我又在琢磨
"Why am I doing this?"
'我为什么要结婚'
And "Who am I doing this for?"
'我结婚是为了谁呢'
Anyway, I just didn't know where to go
我实在不知道去哪儿了
and I know you and I have kinda drifted apart...
虽然咱俩这两年有些疏远
...but you're the only person I know in the city.
但你是我在纽约唯一认识的人了
Who wasn't invited to the wedding.
然后还没收到婚礼邀请
Oh, I was kind of hoping that wouldn't be an issue.
别哪壶不开提哪壶嘛
I'm guessing he bought her the big pipe organ...
肯定是 男主给女主买了那个大管风琴
...and she's really not happy about it.
但是女主很不喜欢
Daddy, I just... I can't marry him.
老爸 我真是...没办法嫁给他
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I just don't love him.
我不爱他了
Well, it matters to me.
这跟我有关系啊
She should not be wearing those pants.
她真不该穿那条裤子
I say push her down the stairs.
赶紧把她推下去得了
Push her down the stairs! Push her down the stairs!
推她...推她...
Come on, Daddy, listen to me!
老爸别这样 听我解释啊
It's like all of my life, everyone's always told me
一直以来 每个人都不停地告诉我
"You're a shoe!
'你是一双鞋'
You're a shoe! You're a shoe! You're a shoe!"
'你是鞋 是鞋 鞋'
Then today I stopped and said, "What if I don't wanna be a shoe?
可是今天我突然想 '如果我不想当一双鞋呢'
What if I wanna be a purse? You know?
如果我想当一个包呢
Or a hat?"
或者当一个帽子
I don't want you to buy me a hat
我不是让你给我买帽子
I am saying I am a hat.
我说我是个帽子
It's a metaphor, Daddy!
这是个比喻 老爸
You can see where he'd have trouble.
我猜是你爸没听懂
Look, Daddy, it's my life.
老爸 这是我自己的人生
Well, maybe I'll just stay here with Monica.
或许我可以和莫妮卡一起住
I guess we've established she's staying with Monica.
我猜 她确定要和莫妮卡住在一起了
Well, maybe that's my decision.
或许这是我自己的决定
Well, maybe I don't need your money.
或许我不需要你的钱了
Wait! Wait! I said maybe!
别挂 我说或许
Okay. Just breathe, that's it.
呼吸 就是这样
Just try to think of nice, calm things.
试着想一些美好 安静的事物
Raindrops on roses and whiskers on kittens
玫瑰的上的雨滴和小猫的胡须
Doorbells and sleigh bells and something with mittens
明亮的铜水壶和羊毛的什么东西
La la la something With string
捆了弦的...啦啦啦
(音乐之声的插曲 这里菲比忘词了)
I'm all better now.
谢谢 我好多了
I helped.
我帮上忙了
Look, this is probably for the best, you know?
嘿 这样其实也不错 你可以...
Independence. Taking control of your life.
...因此独立起来 自己掌控生活
And, hey, if you need anything, you can always come to Joey.
有什么需要的话 尽管来找乔伊
Me and Chandler live right across the hall.
我和钱德就住在对门
And he's away a lot.
而且他经常不在家哦
Joey, stop hitting on her.
别勾引她了 乔伊
It's her wedding day.
人家今天可是要结婚来着
What? Like there's a rule or something?
为啥 有什么规定吗
Please don't do that again. It's a horrible sound.
请别再按了 破铃声难听的要死
-Uh, it's Paul.  -Buzz him in.
-好吧 我是保罗  -让他进来啊
-Who's Paul?  -Paul, the wine guy, Paul?
-保罗是哪位  -那个调酒师吗
Maybe.
你猜
Wait a minute. Your "not a real date" is with
稍等 难道和你吃饭的...
Paul, the wine guy?
是调酒师保罗吗
-He finally asked you out?  -Yes.
-他终于约你出去了  -是啊
Ooh. This is a "Dear Diary" moment.
真是载入史册的一刻
Rach, wait, I can cancel.
瑞秋 我也不是非去不可
Please, no. Go, I'll be fine.
快去吧 我没事的
Ross, are you okay? I mean, do you want me to stay?
罗斯 用我留下来陪你吗
That'd be good.
那样最好了
-Really?  -No, go on! It's Paul, the wine guy.
-真的吗  -逗你的 这可是调酒师保罗啊
Hi, come in, Paul this is...
嗨 快进来 这是...
...everybody. Everybody, this is Paul.
...所有人 你们 这就是保罗
Paul, the wine guy.
调酒师保罗
-Wine guy.  -I didn't catch your name. Paul, was it?
-调酒师啊  -抱歉 我没听清 你是叫保罗来着吗
Okay. Sit down. Two seconds.
你先坐会儿 等我两秒钟
Ooh, I just pulled out four eyelashes. That can't be good.
我刚拔出来四根眼睫毛 不是什么好兆头啊
So, Rachel, what are you up to tonight?
瑞秋 你今晚有什么安排吗
Well, I was supposed to be headed for Aruba on my honeymoon...
我想想 本来是计划坐飞机去阿鲁巴度蜜月的
...so, nothing.
所以 没安排
Right. You're not even getting your honeymoon.
真惨 你连蜜月都还没度呢
God. No, no. Although, Aruba. Heh. This time of year? Eh.
抱歉 我的意思是 阿鲁巴在这个季节挺烂的
Talk about your...
竟是一些...
...big lizards.
...大蜥蜴什么的
Anyway, if you don't feel like being alone tonight...
总之 如果你不想一个人呆着...
...Joey and Chandler are helping me with my furniture.
乔伊和钱德 今晚要来帮我装家具
Yes, and we're very excited about it.
没错 我们为此很兴奋
Actually, thanks, but I'm just gonna hang out here tonight.
谢谢 不过我还是在这儿呆着吧
-It's been a long day.  -Oh, sure. Okay. Sure.
-今天挺累的  -哦 好吧 注意休息
Hey, Pheebs, you wanna help?
嘿 菲比 你要来帮忙吗
Oh, I wish I could, but I don't want to.
我希望我能去 不过我不想去
I'm supposed to attach a bracket-y thing to the side things...
我应该用这些螺丝钉 把这个支架...
...using a bunch of these little worm guys.
...固定在侧面
I have no bracket-y thing, I see no worm guys whatsoever...
我没找到支架 也没看见哪儿有螺丝钉
...and I cannot feel my legs.
而且我的腿麻了
What's this?
这是干什么用的
I have no idea.
你问我 我问谁去啊
-Done with the bookcase.  -All finished.
-书架弄好了  -一切顺利
This was Carol's favorite beer.
这是卡罗最爱喝的啤酒
She always drank it out of the can. I should have known.
她总是倒出来喝 我早该意识到的
Ross, let me ask you a question.
罗斯 我问你个问题
She got the furniture, the stereo, the good TV.
卡罗搬走了家具 音响 和那个酷毙了的电视
What did you get?
你留下什么了
You guys.
你们啊
-Oh, God. Oh, my God.  -You got screwed.
-我靠  -你真是脑残啊
-Oh, my God.  -I know, I know. I'm such an idiot.
-天啊  -我知道 我当时挺傻的
I guess I should've caught on when she went to the dentist
我早该意识到的 她当时一周要去...
...four and five times a week.
...找好几次牙医
I mean, how clean can teeth get?
正常人的牙哪儿用那么白啊
My brother's going through that. He's such a mess.
我哥哥也在经历这些 失魂落魄的
How did you get through it?
你最后怎么走出来的
He might try accidentally breaking something valuable of hers.
他可以试试 失手弄坏她贵重的东西
-Say her...  -Leg?
-比如说...  -她的腿吗
That's one way of going through it, yeah.
这确实也是一种选择
Me, I went for the watch.
不过我当时选了手表
-You actually broke her watch?  -Mm.
-你把她的手表打碎了  -对
Barry, I'm sorry. I am so sorry.
巴瑞 我很抱歉 真的对不起
You probably think it's about making love with your socks on, but it isn't.
你可能误会 这跟你穿着袜子做爱有关 不过真的不是
It isn't, it's about me. And I...
这都是我的错 而且我...
Hi. Machine cut me off again. Anyway...
嗨 电话又断线了 总之...
You know what's scary?
知道我害怕什么吗
What if there's only one woman for everybody?
如果真命天女只有一个怎么办
I mean, what if you get one woman, and that's it?
真正适合你的女人 会不会只有一个
Unfortunately, in my case, there was only one woman for her.
不幸的是 我的女人找到了她的...真命天女
What are you talking about? One woman.
你在说些什么啊 只有一个女人
That's like saying there's only one flavor of ice cream for you.
这就像说 只有一种口味的冰淇淋适合你一样
Let me tell you something, Ross. There's lots of flavors out there.
我告诉你吧 还有好多不同的口味在等着你呢
There's rocky road and cookie dough and...
比如石板街 曲奇豆之类的口味 还有...
...bing cherry vanilla.
...香草味什么的
You can get them with jimmies or nuts or whipped cream.
吃的时候还能配上巧克力粉 果仁 或者奶油
This is the best thing that ever happened to you.
所以说你这是 塞翁失马 焉知非福啊
You got married. You were like, what, 8?
你结婚的时候才多大...8岁吗
Welcome back to the world. Grab a spoon.
欢迎回来 拿起勺子奔向新目标吧
I honestly don't know if I'm hungry or horny.
我都不知道 应该找冰淇淋还是妹子了
Then stay out of my freezer.
那离我家的冰箱远点
Ever since she walked out on me, I...
自从她离开我之后...
What? What?
怎么了 然后呢
You wanna spell it out with noodles?
你打算边吃边说吗
No, it's more of a fifth date kind of revelation.
没有 只是这有点像 第五次约会时的告白
Oh, so there's gonna be a fifth date?
你的意思是还会有第五次约会吗
Isn't there?
你说呢
Yeah, yeah. I think there is.
有 我觉得可以有
What were you gonna say?
你刚才想说什么来着
Ever since she left me...
自从她离开我之后
...I haven't been able to perform...
我一直无法去做一些...
...sexually.
...性福的事情
Oh, God! I am so...
天啊 真是...
-I'm so sorry.  -It's okay.
-...太抱歉了  -没关系的
Being spit on is probably not what you need right now.
你现在需要的应该不是被喷一身水
How long?
有多长时间了啊
Two years.
两年了
I'm glad you smashed her watch.
那她的手表坏的真不冤枉
So you still think you might want that fifth date?
那...你现在觉得 还会有第五次约会吗
Yeah.
当然
Yeah, I do.
会有的
I, Joanie, take you, Charles, as my lawful husband.
我原意把你当做我唯一合法的丈夫
Oh! See.
看看这一对
But Joanie loved Chachi.
可是他俩是相爱的啊
That's the difference.
这就是区别
"Grab a spoon."
拿起勺子
Do you know long it's been since I grabbed a spoon?
你知道我多久没拿勺子了吗
Do the words, "Billy, don't be a hero," mean anything to you?
'比利 不要当个英雄' 对你没有任何启发吗
(著名反战歌曲  这里罗斯把找新女友比喻成上战场)
You know, here's the thing. Even if I could get it together enough...
还有一个问题 就算我能走出来
...to ask a woman out...
有勇气去找新的妹子
...who am I gonna ask?
我该找谁呢
"Sky Blue And Black"-Jackson Browne
"If you ever need holding"
"Call my name, and I'll be there."
Isn't this amazing?
这是不是很神奇
I mean, I have never made coffee before in my life.
我从来都没有自己煮过咖啡
-That is amazing.  -Congratulations.
-那确实很神奇  -恭喜你了
While you're on a roll, if you feel like you gotta make a Western omelet or something...
你正在进入角色 可以试着做个蛋卷什么的
Although, actually I'm really not that hungry this morning.
我今天早上貌似没那么饿
-Good morning.  -Good morning.
-早安  -早安
Morning.
早啊
-Morning.  -Morning, Paul.
-各位早  -早啊 保罗
-Hello, Paul.  -Hi. Paul, is it?
-你好啊 保罗  -是叫保罗来着吗
I had a really great time last night.
昨晚真是棒极了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
我才应该好好感谢你
-We'll talk later, okay?  -Yeah.
-一会儿见  -好的
Thank you.
谢谢
That wasn't a real date.
还说不是个约会
What the hell do you do on a real date?
那你约会的时候都干啥
-Shut up and put my table back.  -Okay.
-闭嘴 把我的桌子搬回去  -好吧
All right, kids, I gotta get to work.
好了 少年们 我要去上班了
If I don't input those numbers
要是我不去录入那些数据的话
it doesn't make much of a difference.
其实也没什么影响
So, like, you guys all have jobs?
你们大家都有工作吗
Yeah, we all have jobs.
对啊 我们都上班
See, that's how we buy stuff.
所以我们才有钱买东西
Yeah, I'm an actor.
对 我是个演员
Would I have seen you in anything?
哇 我看到过你吗
Oh, I doubt it. Mostly regional work.
大概没有 多数是地区性的节目
Unless you happened to catch the Wee One's production of Pinocchio.
除非你看过匹诺曹的重播
"Look, Geppeto. I'm a real live boy."
'看啊葛佩托 我是一个真正的男孩儿了'
I will not take this abuse.
这种羞辱对我没影响
You're right. I'm sorry.
你说得对 抱歉
Once I was a wooden boy. A little wooden boy
'我曾是个小木偶 小木偶啊小木偶'
So how are you doing today? Did you sleep okay?
今天感觉如何 昨晚睡的还好吗
Did you talk to Barry? I can't stop smiling.
和巴瑞谈过了吗 我真是止不住的想笑啊
I can see that. You look like you slept with a hanger in your mouth.
看出来了 你嘴里好像塞了衣架一样
I know. He's just so...
是啊 保罗真是...
Remember you and Tony De Marco?
还记得你和托尼吗
-Oh, yeah.  -Well, it's like that. With feelings.
-当然  -我就和你当时的感觉一样
Oh, wow, are you in trouble!
哇 那你可有麻烦了
Okay, okay. I am just going to get up, go to work...
好了 我现在要站起来 去工作
...and not think about him all day.
然后尽量一天不去想他
Or else I'm just gonna get up and go to work.
或者只是站起来去工作
-Oh, wish me luck!  -What for?
-对了 祝我好运吧  -为了啥
I'm gonna go get one of those job things.
我打算去找一份...工作什么的
-Hey, Monica.  -Hey, Franny. Welcome back.
-嘿 莫妮卡  -欢迎回来 法兰妮
How was Florida?
佛罗里达玩的还好吗
You had sex, didn't you?
你做爱了吧
How do you do that?
你怎么知道的
-So, who?  -You know Paul?
-和谁啊  -你知道保罗吗
Paul, the wine guy?
调酒的那个保罗吗
Oh, yeah, I know Paul.
我当然认识了
You mean, you know Paul like I know Paul?
你和他很熟吗
Are you kidding? I take credit for Paul.
当然 保罗还欠我一个人情呢
Before me, there was no snap in his turtle for two years.
在我之前 他可是两年都没做过爱了
Of course it was a line.
这显然是在撒谎嘛
Why? Why would anybody do something like that?
为什么会有人这样啊
We're looking for an answer more sophisticated than:
说的复杂一点的话 就是...
"To get you into bed."
想要骗你上床
Is it me?
是我的原因吗
Is it like I have some sort of beacon that...
是不是我身上有特殊的气味
...only dogs and men with severe emotional problems can hear?
能吸引来狗和脑残啊
All right, come here. Give me your feet.
别伤心了 来把脚给我
I just thought he was nice, you know?
还以为他会是个好男人
I can't believe you didn't know it was a line.
这也能被骗 真逗
Guess what.
你们猜怎么着
-You got a job?  -Are you kidding?
-找到工作了  -别逗了
I'm trained for nothing.
我什么都不会
I was laughed out of 12 interviews today.
今天去了12个面试全都贻笑大方了
Yet you're surprisingly upbeat.
可是你还依旧神采飞扬
Well, you would be too if you found Joan and David boots on sale...
如果你发现有名牌皮靴打折的话 你也会这样的
...50 percent off.
打了5折啊
Oh, how well you know me.
你还真是了解我
They're my new "I don't need a job or my parents.
这就是我的新皮靴 我不需要工作
I've got great boots" boots.
我也不需要父母
How'd you pay for them?
你拿啥买的这些
Credit card.
信用卡啊
And who pays for that?
那谁还信用卡呢
Um, my father.
我老爸
You can't live off your parents your whole life.
来吧 你不能啃老一辈子
I know that. That's why I was getting married.
我知道 所以我才要结婚的
Give her a break. It's hard being on your own for the first time.
放过她吧 第一次独立是很难的
-Thank you.  -You're welcome.
-谢谢你  -不用客气
I remember when I first came to this city, I was 14.
我第一次来这个城市的时候才14岁
My mom had killed herself and my step-dad was back in prison.
当时我妈自杀了 而我的继父还呆在监狱里
And I got here, and I didn't know anybody.
我当时真的是举目无亲
I ended up living with this albino guy who was cleaning windshields...
我后来和一个白化病人住在一起 他以...
...outside Port Authority. And then he killed himself.
...为港务局清洗车窗为生  后来他也自杀了
And then I found aromatherapy. So believe me, I know exactly how you feel.
之后我才找到了按摩的工作 所以我完全理解你现在的心情
The word you're looking for is:
你现在需要的是...
"Anyway..."
总之...
All right. You ready?
好的 你准备好了吗
-I don't think so.  -Oh, come on.
-我觉得还没有  -别磨蹭了
Cut. Cut.
剪 剪
Cut, cut, cut.
剪 剪...
Welcome to the real world.
欢迎来到现实世界
It sucks. You're gonna love it.
很烂 不过你会爱上它的
Well, that's it. You gonna crash on the couch?
今晚就到这吧 你要在沙发上睡吗
-No. No, I gotta go home sometime.  -Are you gonna be okay?
-不用了 我待会就回去  -你还好吧
Yeah.
没事了
Look what I just found on the floor.
莫妮卡 这是啥
What?
是什么啊
That's Paul's watch.
那是保罗的手表
You can just put it back where you found it.
你把它放回去就行了
Oh, boy. All right. Good night, everybody.
晚安了各位 我要去睡觉了
-Oh, sorry.  -No. Oh, no. Go.
-不好意思  -没事 你吃吧
-No, have it, really.  -Split it?
-还是给你吧  -分着吃吗
-Okay.  -Okay.
-好吧  -好的
You probably didn't know this, but back in high school I had...
有件事你可能不知道 在中学的时候我...
...a major crush on you.
...曾经暗恋过你
I knew.
我知道
You did?
这都知道
I figured you thought I was Monica's geeky older brother.
我以为你只当我是 莫妮卡的怪哥哥呢
I did.
确实
Listen, do you think...
我想问个问题
And try not to let my vulnerability become any kind of a factor here.
不用担心会伤害到我
Do you think it would be okay if I ask you out sometime, maybe?
我以后能约你出去吗 有可能吗
Yeah.
可以
Maybe.
或许吧
Okay.
好的
Okay, maybe I will.
或许我会的
-Good night.  -Good night.
-晚安了  -晚安
See you.
路上慢点啊
Wait, wait. Hey, what's with you?
等会儿 你这是怎么了
I just grabbed a spoon.
我拿起了支勺子
I can't believe what I'm hearing here.
我真不敢相信我的耳朵
I can't believe What I'm hearing here
-What? I said you had...  -What? I said you had...
-有吗 我说你...  -有吗 我说你...
Would you stop?
能别这样吗
Oh, was I doing it again?
我老毛病又犯了
Yes.
是啊
Would anybody like more coffee?
有人想要续杯吗
Did you make it or are you just serving it?
你是负责煮 还是负责端
-I'm just serving it.  -I'll have a cup of coffee.
-我是负责端的  -那给我来一杯
Kids, new dream.
我又做了个新梦
I'm in Las Vegas. I'm Liza Minnelli.
我在赌城而且摇身一变成了莉萨·米娜丽